[microphone feedback]
[♪ opening theme music playing]
FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[Ahin] There's a ghost
in the abandoned house.
I'm sure it's some kind of vengeful ghost.
It's asking us to catch the killer.
-Let's go check it out.
-What?
PREVIOUSLY
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Isoo exhales]
[Hyera] You check upstairs.
[blunt thuds]
Nutjob!
-Yes, ma'am!
-[Hyera grunts]
[Isoo] What's going on?
-Hey, what happened?
-I don't know.
I got attacked out of nowhere.
[♪ upbeat suspenseful music playing]
-One... Two, three!
-Two, three!
[Hyera grunts]
[glass shattering]
[explosion]
I seriously almost died.
There really is something here.
I have great instincts, huh?
Let's open it up.
There's definitely something in there.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
You were there.
I started the fire.
They might've found something
while putting out the fire.
Hyeonsu disappeared.
Hyeonsu's last location was that house.
[Changun] You uncovered five bodies?
Yes, they're performing the autopsy now.
[Dr. Yoon] We performed the autopsy
on the most recent victim first.
The most recently deceased victim
had these glasses in their pants.
These belong to Park Hyeonsu.
Three months ago, at Yuseon-dong...
-[muffled screaming]
-[flesh squelching]
[Byungsik] ...Kim Minseo was murdered.
[Kim Suwon] Park Hyeonsu's fingerprints
were on a knife at the scene.
That knife was the knife
missing from Park Hyeonsu's house.
MURDER SUSPECT
[Junyoung] Wait, so,
the murder suspect you were after
three months ago was murdered
and his body was found
at the abandoned house?
What if Park Hyeonsu wasn't the one
who killed Kim Minseo?
It's the perfect crime.
The target.
A victim to frame as the suspect.
If they kill the target and the suspect,
then make him go missing,
the case cannot be solved.
[Hyera] Five perfect crimes.
You need at least two people
to make this possible.
-They're methodical and cold.
-[Hyeonsu grunting]
[Kyungjin] So they're
professional killers?
If they came to the house...
It means they killed someone else.
They were there to bury the body.
[Jaechun] It's blood. [exclaims]
KILLER 1
JANG JAECHUN
It leaked.
KILLER 2
JO BEOMKI
What do we do?
Taegwang.
THE KILLER OF KILLERS
YU TAEGWANG
[♪ tense music playing]
But don't courier deliveries come quickly
and drop it off at the door?
They're a bit different
from parcel deliveries.
They usually hand it to you.
Uh-huh.
Then the victim must have known
a courier was coming.
Yes, they usually contact ahead.
But this wasn't a real courier.
So someone must've helped them.
To make her open the door.
It must be the one she lives with.
Her husband.
Who is her husband?
Nam Jaeguk.
He's the CEO of a furniture company.
IDENTITY RECORD
NAM JAEGUK
Detective Choi, you look into Nam Jaeguk.
And check
if Kim Minseo had life insurance.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Detective Park.
You look into the stalking case.
Understood.
We'll meet Nam Jaeguk tomorrow.
Okay.
[Hyera] We're with the police.
Is Mr. Nam Jaeguk here?
Yes, what is this about?
Well, his wife was brutally murdered.
Do you happen to know anything?
Like the CEO's secret, for example?
[chuckles softly] You think I'd know that?
Please take us to see him.
EPISODE 4
Don't go probing just anyone.
This is an investigation technique.
Didn't you know? Huh?
[mutters] Honestly.
[♪ tense music playing]
KIM MINSEO'S HUSBAND
NAM JAEGUK
What...
is this about?
We're here about your wife's case.
You're not the detective in charge.
We're reinvestigating
the case from scratch.
Reinvestigating?
Park Hyeonsu's the culprit.
Isn't he?
Mmm. Someone else might be the culprit.
-Couldn't they?
-[scoffs]
[Hyera] We heard your wife
was being stalked.
Was the stalker Park Hyeonsu?
Yes. [sighs]
I've already told the police all this.
Don't you share information?
[scoffs]
Please tell us again.
Did you hear anything about Park Hyeonsu?
[Jaeguk inhales deeply]
They dated briefly in college,
then ran into each other
by chance recently.
After that, he followed her around,
trying to get back together.
That's what she said.
You mean your wife,
Ms. Kim Minseo, said that herself?
Yes, she did.
Why are you bringing this up again now?
Park Hyeonsu
has been found.
How did you find him?
Mmm, I can't tell you.
That's classified information.
We came to update you on your wife's case.
We'll be in touch.
Her husband definitely ordered the murder.
How do you know?
"I am guilty"
was written all over his face.
That was pretty much a confession.
There's something else.
-What?
-When we said Park Hyeonsu had been found,
he didn't ask if we'd caught him.
How did you find him?
Right, that's true.
His first concern should've been
whether we'd caught the guy.
-It's because he knows the guy's dead.
-[softly] Hmm.
Hey, take care.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[breathing raggedly]
Where's my damn phone?
[man] After today, you mustn't
call me, no matter what happens.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[exhales deeply]
During the month
before Ms. Kim Minseo died,
she filed three stalking reports.
STALKING REPORT
Did you question the suspect?
No, we weren't able to.
She didn't know who it was.
She just reported that someone had been
following her near her house.
Ah, for the last report,
she deliberately caused a fender bender
because someone was following her.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
10 DAYS BEFORE KIM MINSEO'S DEATH
Hello, we're responding to a report.
Yes, I did cause the accident,
but I think that man in the car behind me
has been stalking me for a few days now.
That's why I did it.
What are you talking about?
Hey, lady.
Why would I follow you around?
You have. You've been following me.
Lady, are you crazy? Delusional much?
[officer] But...
Both of you, please calm down.
Why would I follow you?
Don't be ridiculous.
IDENTITY RECORD
LEE KYUNGSU
[line connects, ringing]
Kyungjin, get a location on this number.
010-0675-0040.
PARK HYEONSU'S HOUSE
Did you find anything?
Just some fingerprints
and a few strands of hair.
-Please run them as quickly as possible.
-Got it.
Hey.
KIM MINSEO 4:00 P.M.
They met three months before the incident.
Why did they meet?
They had no contact before.
Hmm...
[♪ gripping music playing]
-Found it.
-[mouse clicking]
[Minseo] This is Minseo.
It's been a while.
I hope you've been well.
I heard you became a lawyer.
I want to ask your advice on something.
Could we possibly meet?
I need your help.
Kim Minseo was the one
who asked to meet first.
Why?
Because of this?
[♪ upbeat jaunty music playing]
[Isoo] Look familiar?
-[scoffs]
-[chuckles softly]
I don't go around
probing people for no reason.
It's my detective's instinct.
[in English] Understand?
Mmm-hmm. Mmm.
[camera beeping, shutter clicking]
[gasps softly]
[in Korean] Who are you?
Police.
I haven't done anything wrong.
You're parked illegally, for one.
Am I getting a ticket?
Did you follow this person?
[sighs]
Is that your answer?
Yes, I followed her.
What about this man?
I took pictures of them meeting.
Who hired you?
[exclaims] How would I know that?
It's just a part-time gig I do sometimes.
Besides, I don't work with them anymore.
-Why not?
-[sighs softly]
That woman died after I took those photos.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
It kept bothering me.
It felt weird from the start.
I was told to get proof
they were having an affair,
but all they did
was drink coffee and talk.
They didn't even seem close.
[sighs softly]
Where was that place you worked?
I'll start the briefing.
Nam Jaeguk married Kim Minseo in 2021.
The furniture company he runs
was originally his father-in-law's.
And Kim Minseo's life insurance payout
is one billion won.
He became a CEO thanks to his in-laws.
[exhales deeply]
Then killed her for the insurance payout?
Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
He's worse than that.
-[scoffs]
-[Isoo] He even cheated on her.
With his secretary.
This is straight out of a soap opera.
Kim Minseo knew about the affair
and wanted a divorce,
which is why she met Park Hyeonsu.
[bangs table]
Rather than get fired and end up divorced,
Nam Jaeguk chose to kill his wife.
It's clear that Nam Jaeguk was the one
who hired someone to kill Kim Minseo.
The question is, who did he hire?
There's a PI involved.
A top PI, apparently.
What's this?
A top PI?
The stalker Kim Minseo reported
used to work here.
All he did was tail her.
He took photos of her
meeting Park Hyeonsu.
He doesn't look like a top PI.
He looks kind of dopey.
His name is Myeong Seokho.
Two fraud convictions.
Let's go catch that dopey PI!
Oh. Don't you dare.
Why not?
He can just deny it.
What if he says
they were just hired to tail her?
[Byungsik] She's right.
We don't have any evidence.
Myeong Seokho may have planned it,
but someone else did the work.
If we want to catch them...
We should just hire them ourselves.
Let's hire them to kill someone.
[Junyoung] Right.
We'll plant a bug,
then wait until the hitmen call.
If we trace it, we'll get their location.
[scoffs softly]
Is this how you normally investigate?
Hey, it's a trade secret.
[chuckles softly] I know it seems
a little weird, but it does work.
You know our track record.
[♪ quirky music playing]
[sighs softly]
Come on, we have no evidence.
What if they run?
[clock ticking rapidly]
[sighs]
Fine. Let's try it.
[Junyoung] Okay.
Then, shall I pose as the client?
Mm-mm. You did it last season.
We need someone who looks like
they've got some kind of a past.
[sighs]
Did any theater as a kid?
No.
My hands start shaking
when I'm dealt a decent hand in poker.
[chuckles softly]
[breathes sharply]
It should be someone older.
And look like they'd want someone dead.
Someone with that
cold-blooded mobster vibe.
Does no one fit that bill?
What are you all doing? Where's my update?
[chuckles softly]
Oh...
He looks like he could act.
[cell phone vibrating]
[chuckles softly]
-Yes, Detective Jin.
-[Isoo] Mr. Choi.
-I need to borrow your car.
-My car?
Right now. There's no time.
Send it to the station.
What are you...
We've got hitmen to catch.
There's a suit in the car, right?
I need a suit and a watch. Right now.
[♪ quirky dramatic music playing]
[exhales]
[inhales deeply]
Stop the car.
Another car will be here shortly.
I'm sorry, sir.
Not at all.
I'm used to this.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
[Taegyun] Who is that?
Did we arrest a mob boss?
[♪ upbeat swing jazz music playing]
Isn't that Chief Park?
Gosh...
What are they doing?
-[car door closes]
-I have no idea, sir.
There's something wrong
with our whole station.
[sighs in exasperation] Good grief.
MYEONG SEOKHO
[in-game thudding, chiming]
-[in-game Korean chatter]
-[mouse clicks]
[in-game fanfare]
It's really taking a nosedive.
[♪ tense music playing]
[door closes, locks]
Who are you?
[Changun grunts]
[metal cupboard clangs]
[Changun exhales deeply]
Would you like something to drink?
[in a raspy voice, in English] Cold brew.
Decaf.
Light vanilla.
Toffee nut latte.
French pistachio.
[in Korean] Frappe, served hot.
-Fra...
-Okay. [chuckles nervously]
I'll go get them right away.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
What in the...
How can I help you?
I've got someone to find.
I heard
you're good at finding people.
Oh, yes, well.
We are the best in the business.
[wicked laughter sounds]
What did he do?
He stole...
my stash.
What stash?
What do you think? Foot cream?
Ah.
[♪ tense, dramatic music playing]
Then, let's see.
We'll sign a contract first. Your name is?
[clears throat]
[laughing menacingly]
You want to know...
my name?
The hell's wrong with you?
Uh... No.
[chuckles nervously]
No contract necessary.
[exhales nervously]
I'll find him no matter what.
[grunts softly]
[♪ quirky dramatic music playing]
Your advance.
Whoa!
You have three days.
If you haven't found him by then...
[thuds]
Cozy office you've got here.
[♪ tense music playing]
Half a can of gas
will wipe this place out.
If you're unlucky,
someone might die.
[gulps nervously]
[tremulously] I won't let you down.
Let's go.
Yes, boss.
That stings.
[exclaims]
Have a good night, sir.
[♪ quirky music playing]
[car alarm chirps]
[exhales heavily]
[in normal voice] That was scary.
Chief, you were amazing.
That was convincing as hell.
You should be an actor.
I was in the drama club in high school.
The Drama Lovers Club.
-[scoffs incredulously]
-I knew it. You were a real scumbag.
-That's a compliment, right?
-[both chuckle]
Let's go.
Will he buy it, or will he not?
-That is the question.
-[Isoo] Let's go.
Have a good night, boss.
-[Junyoung] Thank you, sir.
-Right, keep at it.
Hey, any movements?
No.
[♪ tense suspenseful music playing]
GANGHA 3-DONG ABANDONED HOUSE FIRE
SCENE OF PAST HOMICIDE
STILL DETERMINING THE CAUSE OF THE FIRE
[Beomki exclaims]
[whimpers]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[panting softly]
Fingerprints.
[♪ tense music playing]
[sniffles]
[coughing weakly]
[groaning]
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[breath trembles, mutters]
[Kim Suwon] Looks like a burner phone.
[Isoo sighs]
[line ringing]
Hey.
We got a new job. Where are you?
[♪ gripping suspenseful music playing]
The reservoir?
You still haven't taken care of that?
Someone set fire to our burial site.
What are you talking about?
There were cops there.
Those useless morons.
They got scared and couldn't kill them.
They just tied them up and bailed.
But then,
looks like someone set it on fire.
Wait, so do we make a run for it?
Why? They found nothing.
Who's the client?
I don't know.
Some kind of drug cartel.
He wants me to find someone.
What's his name?
I don't know that either.
If I don't find him in three days,
he said he'll set this place on fire.
[scoffs]
He's a cop.
[♪ tense music playing]
A cop?
[Junyoung and Kyungjin sigh]
[sighs softly]
[sighs]
They must've found the bodies
at our burial site.
[splutters] Then what do we do?
Don't be scared.
They won't find any evidence.
But what about me? What do I do?
Burn all the records and go off the grid.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[Jaechun and Beomki grunting]
[Jaechun panting]
Your phones.
[snorts, sniffles]
[Jaechun snorts]
[sighs contentedly]
We're flying out at dawn.
Let's go on vacation.
Where do you wanna go?
[sniffles]
[chuckles softly]
[Jaechun and Beomki chuckle]
[♪ tense music playing]
-Hey, get all the files out.
-What?
[yelling] Get all the files out,
right now!
Yes, okay.
[mutters frantically]
Freeze.
Damn it.
[♪ tense pulsating music playing]
[Isoo inhales sharply, exhales]
[gate clangs]
[device beeps]
[Seokho, over recorder] The reservoir?
You still haven't taken care of that?
Where's this reservoir?
This is illegal wiretapping!
This won't hold up
as evidence in court anyway.
You know that! Right?
You sure we won't find
any evidence over there?
I doubt it.
[Byungsik sighs]
Right now,
I'm in a real bad mood
because you played me.
While we investigate that,
the real killers will get away.
Then you'll become the main culprit.
No, but... You have no evidence!
Let's see the evidence.
-What's your name?
-What?
Your name.
Lee Eunjeong.
Right, Eunjeong.
Got a boyfriend?
Yes, we're planning to get married.
That's a shame.
Congratulations.
[inhales sharply]
But will he wait a decade for you?
-What?
-This is a hitman's office.
Over five people have been killed already.
Even if you're just a minor accomplice,
you'd get at least 10 years. Right?
-Of course.
-For sure.
[Eunjeong] No, I...
I don't know anything.
I just took calls and made coffee.
I don't know if the judge
will believe that. [clicks tongue]
Unless you help us catch the bad guys.
Yeongil Reservoir. It's Yeongil Reservoir.
I heard Mr. Myeong mention it once.
-You idiot.
-Sit down!
[♪ upbeat quirky music playing]
They would've bolted by now.
-I'll go check it out.
-Got it.
-[Byungsik] Let's go.
-[team] Yes, sir.
You must be in shock. Here, drink this.
Can I go home now?
Of course not. We have to question you.
[Eunjeong] What?
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
Gwangjin-gu, Seoul. Lee Eunjeong.
You're Korean, right?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You know the victim, Kim Minseo, right?
I don't know. I really don't know her.
You ordered Lee Kyungsu
to tail Ms. Kim Minseo, didn't you?
Come on, stop saying you don't know.
You and that dopey PI...
[sobbing] I really don't know.
Oh, my God, I want to go home.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[KCSI officer 1] They torched
the whole thing.
[Byungsik sighs heavily]
[KCSI officer 2] There's a suitcase
in the trunk.
It's that car.
Please keep tracking them.
[officer] Got it.
There's nothing.
I need the blue light.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[line connects, ringing]
Detective Joo.
We got a fingerprint.
SCANNING
[digital beeps]
[Hyera] Jang Jaechun.
NAME: JANG JAECHUN
[Junyoung] "Seongju State Prison."
Seongju State Prison?
[♪ tense pulsating music playing]
2019 SEONGJU STATE PRISON
He was in the same prison
as Myeong Seokho.
Let's look into Jang Jaechun.
I'll contact the prison.
I'll look into his family.
A phone was found at the reservoir.
We got a fingerprint, too.
You have an accomplice. Who is it?
Forensics will recover everything.
[mutters]
You know how a trial works.
Cooperating with the investigation
and showing signs of remorse
are important considerations in court.
You're out of options now.
Wouldn't it be smarter
to try and reduce your sentence?
[Seokho] So...
His name's Jo Beomki.
He's Jaechun's old classmate.
But all I did was make the introduction.
They asked me for work.
How was I supposed to know
they'd kill someone? I had no idea.
Where are they?
I really don't know.
Did you find anything?
No.
Nothing much.
Myeong Seokho named his accomplice.
-[mouse clicks]
-[keyboard clacking]
JO BEOMKI
Where are they?
He doesn't know.
[sighs softly]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Find out where Jang Jaechun
and Jo Beomki are.
If making introductions
was really all you did,
you shouldn't go down with them.
-[dogs barking distantly]
-[fire crackling]
[cutlery clinking]
[door opens]
[Jaechun exhales deeply]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[grunts]
[Jaechun exclaims]
-[sighs] Granny.
-[Beomki chuckles]
I told you to just go to bed.
[Granny] How can I go to bed
when your friends are here?
-Want me to cook something?
-Nah, just go to sleep already.
Help yourself.
[Beomki] Yes, thank you.
What's this? Kimchi?
-[chuckles] Thank you, Granny. Good night.
-[Granny] Night.
[Beomki] I wish you a long
and healthy life.
[fire continues crackling]
[cell phone vibrating]
INCOMING CALL
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[line ringing]
[cell phone continues vibrating]
[line continues ringing]
[line connects]
Hey.
Where are you?
Somewhere safe. Why? Where are you?
I just checked into a random motel.
Then just hole up in there.
We're getting out of here tomorrow.
Where are you going?
Why do you want to know?
Hey, take me with you.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm freaking out here.
Why are you acting like a moron?
Just lay low for a while,
then make your move. Got it?
Hey, Beomki!
You bastard.
You two are the ones who killed someone.
What are you going to do about this?
[♪ ominous music playing]
We're flying out of Busan
first thing tomorrow.
I'll call you once I'm there.
[♪ tense music playing]
[sighs in exasperation]
What is it?
It's just...
We don't know where they're headed,
and catching someone
at an airport isn't easy.
They're ruthless killers,
so if we're not careful,
civilians could get hurt.
[sighs] We won't be able to stop them
at the entrance.
It'll have to be at security.
-Notify the airport first.
-Got it.
-I'll report to the chief.
-[Junyoung] Okay.
[Kyungjin] I got their location.
I got them as far as Wonsan-eup in Daegu,
but nothing after that.
Wonsan-eup, Daegu?
FAMILY RECORDS
JANG JAECHUN
Wonsan-eup, Daegu.
Jang's grandma lives there.
[♪ tense music playing]
[mouse clicks]
SATELLITE MAP SEARCH
4-26 DURE-GIL, WONSAN-EUP, DAEGU
That's right. I got them as far as here.
Let's go catch them now.
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
Let's go!
Move out.
-It'll take 3 hours and 20 minutes.
-Huh?
-Hold on.
-[tires screech]
That's way too long.
These guys are smart.
What if they catch on and bolt?
Then what else can we do?
[sighs deeply]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[cell phone vibrating]
Yes, Detective Jin.
[Isoo] Mr. Choi, where are you?
I'm in the helicopter.
I was in Ulsan until now.
No way.
I need the chopper.
Bring it to the station.
What?
I need to catch some hitmen.
Please be quick.
-[line disconnects]
-[sighs in exasperation]
Turn the chopper around.
[helicopter whirring]
I'll get a car here right away.
[chuckles softly]
[sighs wearily]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[Seokho] Beomki!
If we somehow get found out,
then we kill those two
and the two of us just disappear.
If I ever call you "Beomki,"
that's the signal.
[sniffles]
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
There it is.
-Get ready.
-Yes, ma'am.
Yes, ma'am.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[water running]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[Taegwang breathing heavily]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[continues breathing heavily]
[Granny] Jaechun, is that you?
[♪ ominous music playing]
[door creaking]
[gate clangs]
What happened here?
[panting]
[door creaking]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[whispering] Detective Joo.
[Kyungjin] Ma'am.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[gasps, grunts]
[all sigh in relief]
Who are you?
[♪ somber music playing]
Stay with her.
Got it.
[door creaking, closes]
Ma'am, we're police officers.
What?
Why are you here?
Did Jaechun do something bad again?
Well...
[Hyera] Yes, please send
the forensics team.
They're both dead.
[Junyoung] I need a patrol unit
and an ambulance here.
There's also an elderly lady here,
and she's quite shaken up.
We'll need backup.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
They haven't been dead long.
-Did they kill each other?
-Why? They were planning to run.
Did they get into a drunken fight?
Killing the suspects
to make it the perfect crime.
[♪ tense pulsating music playing]
There are three kinds of cigarettes.
They haven't been dead long,
so the perp's still here.
Kyungjin, don't come outside.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Oh. It's all right, ma'am.
I'm sure it's nothing.
[Taegwang exclaims]
[blade swishing]
[both grunting]
[Isoo grunting]
[exclaims]
[both grunting]
[objects clattering]
[gunshot]
[panting] The next one's live.
Want to see who's faster,
you or a bullet? Huh?
[Isoo grunts]
[♪ gripping music playing]
[panting]
Jin Isoo!
Please.
[Hyera panting]
[Taegwang groaning]
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
-[groaning]
-Hold still!
[panting] I'm basically a sniper, right?
You should've aimed a little higher.
-Seriously?
-Just kidding.
Good shot.
I taught you well.
That's not what's important here.
-I'm basically John Wick.
-[scoffs]
[groans]
Hey, are you hurt?
It's just a scratch.
[exclaiming in pain]
Hold still. It's to stop the bleeding.
That really hurts. [screams]
-[groans]
-[sighs softly]
[siren blaring distantly]
[Isoo] Oh...
What's that?
Pain medication.
[grunts] Don't give him that.
He needs to suffer a bit more.
Give it to me. I'm in a lot of pain.
[♪ quirky music playing]
You asshole, you.
How dare you throw chilis at me?
Guess you couldn't outrun a bullet, huh?
[muttering] Asshole.
We've become a real married couple.
-That's what I think.
-[both chuckle]
[Isoo] What a lovey-dovey couple, huh?
[in English] Nice weather.
[in Korean] But what a shame.
It's time to say goodbye.
Oh, you even had a baby?
Is it a boy, or a girl?
-[barking]
-[exclaims]
[snarling]
It's a puppy.
It was a puppy.
[Hyera] Nam Jaeguk.
You are hereby under arrest
for soliciting the murder of Kim Minseo.
You have the right to an attorney
and the right to remain silent.
You won't be penalized
for remaining silent.
-Got all that?
-I was just...
-I was taking a walk with my employee.
-Honey.
I was just...
Did you really not know
that your boyfriend killed his wife?
You don't seem that oblivious.
If you didn't know before, now you do.
Someone died because of you.
Mmm. [clicking tongue]
[Jaeguk mutters]
Is it a crime to take a walk...
[exhales deeply]
[van door slides open]
Oh...
You two haven't met before, right?
Say hello. This is... No, this person.
This is the scumbag
who asked you to kill his wife.
And this is the hitman who got the job.
You should become friends.
You'll be cellmates soon.
Let's go.
Yes, ma'am.
-[engine starts]
-[siren blaring]
[♪ upbeat quirky music playing]
[siren blaring]
-[reporter 1] They're here!
-[reporters clamoring]
[tires screech]
[Isoo] Hurry up.
Take his picture.
Here.
[reporters continue clamoring]
-Good job. Thanks.
-Thank you for your hard work.
-Hey, take them away.
-[all] Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Heaven's on my side.
Ah, another case closed.
[reporters continue clamoring]
[reporter 2] Please look this way!
[groans softly]
This way? Where? Like this?
It's not over yet.
Jin Isoo caught them.
It was Jin Isoo.
Now, let's walk through the case
to find out what happened.
Mr. Nam Jaeguk here
was suspicious of his wife and asked for
an investigation into her movements.
-Exactly.
-And Mr. Dopey...
Mr. Myeong Seokho here
gave the job to Mr. Yu Taegwang.
I only made the introduction.
Sir.
[Isoo] Then, Mr. Yu Taegwang,
you committed a murder
nobody hired you to commit.
But how did you know
that Mr. Nam Jaeguk wanted his wife dead?
Are you psychic? Can you read minds?
That's exactly it.
I never asked them to kill her.
For God's sake,
why did you do something so stupid?
[splutters]
[chuckles]
[sighs]
You pieces of shit.
-What the hell did you just...
-I told you.
[♪ tense music playing]
If I go down, we all go down together.
I recorded all the phone calls.
[Seokho] He's called Nam Jaeguk.
He's having an affair.
He wants us to kill his wife
and make it look like a robbery.
[in English] Game over, loser!
-[in Korean] This is a fake voice.
-Get up.
Don't be ridiculous, Mr. Dopey PI.
[Seokho] This is AI-generated!
Want to turn yourself in?
You'll feel better afterward.
It's not a crime to fall in love, right?
I've been in love, too.
It happens. We're only human.
[door closes]
Write down the identities
of the skeletal remains you buried.
Skeletal remains?
I'm not sure what you mean.
Jang Jaechun and Jo Beomki
were the ones who carried out the murders.
But they killed each other,
so your sentence won't be too harsh.
You'll be better off if you cooperate.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[pen clicks]
[pen scratching]
KIM JIHUN, OH SEA, HAN MINJAE
Let me tell you something in return.
That abandoned house
you used as a burial site,
there was a robbery
and murder there 10 years ago.
The killer's DNA was found at the scene,
but there was no suspect
to match it against.
Why would you have used
that place as a burial site?
Is it possible that was your first murder?
DNA ANALYSIS REPORT
The DNA found at the abandoned house
matched your DNA.
Jo Beomki and Jang Jaechun.
You killed them too, didn't you?
And you washed the blood off
in the bathroom.
[breathing heavily]
[Hyera] We found your fingerprint there.
You thought you could play us, didn't you?
The perfect crime?
That doesn't exist.
[doorbell rings]
[door unlocks, beeps]
We're sorry for everything.
The real culprit
has been arrested.
[♪ poignant music playing]
[sniffling]
[sobbing]
[Isoo] "The brave citizen award."
"Park Ahin, of Myeongun Middle School,
Grade 9, Class 1."
"In recognition
of your unwavering support of
and cooperation with law enforcement,
and for your assistance
in the arrest of a dangerous criminal,
we award this commendation."
"February 10, 2025."
"Gwon Taegyun,
Chief of Police, Gangha Police Station."
You're all here.
-Congratulations, Ahin.
-Thank you.
This is a gift from me.
[♪ uplifting music playing]
It's the only one in the world.
Custom-made in 24-karat gold.
[chuckles] I'll study really hard
and become a detective like you.
[Isoo sighs thoughtfully]
That might be a challenge.
The goal of a cool detective like me
might be hard to reach.
Aim for Detective Joo here.
Here, let's meet again as colleagues.
Okay.
[Taegyun] All right, back to work.
I'm off.
-Sir.
-[Taegyun] What?
-We've earned a vacation.
-What do you mean?
You were just doing your duty
as detectives.
Get your photos taken.
We were doing our duty,
but we still busted a murder ring.
[♪ enthralling music playing]
[slow, echoing footsteps]
FLEX X COP 2
EPISODE 4
CONCIERGE MANAGER
OH MINYEONG
[♪ upbeat pop music playing,
Hersh "Shadows In The Night"]
Special Cast.
Lee Hakju, Park Jungpyo, Kwon Seungwoo
Park Soi
[receptionist] Room 709
was unoccupied yesterday.
[Hyera] That room has been vacant
for two months.
[Isoo] Why did she go
to an unoccupied room alone?
-Have you seen anyone suspicious lately?
-The ugly guy?
-Chunsik?
-Isoo!
I asked her out.
The seventh floor camera isn't broken.
I was following the CEO's orders.
There was an assault here last Wednesday.
He tried to drag her into Room 709?
It did seem like
she was seeing someone lately.
[man] I think it was one
of the hotel staff.
[Hyera] Are you going to keep interfering?
[Isoo] What was he doing
with the cameras off?
I found something
that looks like a bloodstain.
Let's go.
The suspect is on the seventh floor.
[Hyera] Watch out! Step on it.
[exclaims]
[man] Yes.
I just arrived.
Yes.
I'll see you tomorrow.
[♪ pensive music playing]
[line disconnects]
The chairman is waiting for you.
I'll be leaving soon.
I have no business with him.
He ordered you to come home.
Korea...
has too many security cameras.
[chuckles softly]
Translated by Hyesoo Lee